nextdaypets.com 2012-11-17

# Privacy Policy | NextDayPets.com

**NEXT DAY PETS, L.L.C. PRIVACY POLICY**

If you have any questions about the privacy policy, please contact us using the Help Center. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Next Day Pets, L.L.C. is the sole owner of the information collected on this Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

In order for a user to access contact information for non-subscribing members and/or place listings the user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name, address, phone number, and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest and may be shared with other companies who use the information in aggregate to gather broad demographic information. We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

Next Day Pets, L.L.C. will take reasonable measures to not disclose the contents of your communications unless required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to: (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Next Day Pets' website; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Next Day Pets or enforce or further the application or intent of the terms of this Agreement; or (iii) act to protect the personal safety of Next Day Pets participants or the public. 

From time to time, Next Day Pets may make various aspects of our database of Your Information available to other parties for promotions of and solicitations for their goods or services that may be of interest to Next Day Pets members. However, we will not distribute personal information about any individual -- in other words, while we might let our advertisers know that we have 1000 people in your zip code, we won't let advertisers know that YOU live in your zip code. However, by accepting this Agreement, you expressly consent to such use and disclosure of non-personally identifiable information. Please note that Next Day Pets maintains the right to send you periodic updates as Next Day Pets deems necessary. Also note that if you provide any information to other parties, or any other sites you encounter on Next Day Pets or the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. We may, however, use and disclose general data and/or statistical data that includes data about you and/or your listings in order to provide better service to you and other users, among other reasons. 

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. Cookies are also used to track promotional discounts on our Site. Next Day Pets, L.L.C. may set and access Next Day Pets, L.L.C. cookies on your computer. Next Day Pets, L.L.C. lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Next Day Pets, L.L.C. cookies. 

**LOG FILES**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**LINKS**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Next Day Pets, L.L.C. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**REFER-A-FRIEND**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Next Day Pets, L.L.C. will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Next Day Pets, L.L.C. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Next Day Pets, L.L.C. to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**SECURITY**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’. To verify our web site security, visit http://www.nextdaypets.com/secure/. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, at a world class facility. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can contact us using the Help Center. 

**SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES**

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone. 

**CORRECTING / UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member account (“my account”) page or visiting our Help Center. 

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

Next Day Pets, L.L.C. may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Next Day Pets, L.L.C. account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**ACCEPTANCE**

By accepting the User Agreement you expressly agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy and to receive this information described herein. If you break the law, we may have to disclose your personal information to the authorities. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

**THIRD PARTY COOKIES**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
